tix.com 2008-12-16

# Tix - Box Office Software and Online Ticket Sales

### Privacy Policy

**Scope** This Privacy Policy covers Tix treatment of personally identifiable information that Tix collects when you are on the Tix web site ("Site"). This policy does not cover the treatment of personally identifiable information that may be collected by other web sites ("Third-Party Sites") that Tix links to or is otherwise affiliated with.

**Information Collection and Use** Tix collects personally identifiable information when you register for an account or purchase products or services. Tix also collects information from your browser including browser type, browser version, browser settings, operating system, pages visited, your IP Address, and Cookies. Tix uses this information for general purposes such as allowing you to add products and services to your shopping cart, tailoring the content within the Site to match your interests, and ensuring that the site continues to operate properly with commonly used operating systems and browsers. Your IP Address will be stored and used for security purposes to prevent fraud and other illegal activity.

Children under the age of 13 are prohibited from submitting personal information to Tix. Federal Law prohibits websites from collecting and/or distributing personal information from children without parental consent. At this time, Tix has no effective means to obtain and track parental consent. Therefore, Tix must prohibit the submission of personal information from children under the age of 13.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure** Tix will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. Tix may need to send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people in order to provide you with a product or service you've requested. Tix may also send your personal information to others when required to do so by law.

**Mailing List** The mailing list is a list that may be used by Tix and/or the organizations using Tix to sell tickets. This mailing list may be used to inform you of upcoming events and/or special promotions. You have the option of opting out of the mailing list at anytime. Tix will not send marketing or other solicitations to patrons that have chosen not to be included on the mailing list. Organizations using Tix to sell tickets are prohibited from sending marketing or other solicitations to those customer that have chosen not to be included on the mailing list. Regardless of whether you've opted out of the mailing list, Tix and/or the organizations using Tix to sell tickets may contact you regarding important information related to an event you've already purchased tickets to. This may include important information such as an event cancellation, postponement, or relocation. It may also include a question or problem related to your order or payment. Season ticket holders may also be contacted regarding annual season ticket renewals regardless of whether or not they've chosen to be included on the mailing list.

**Cookies** Cookies are small text files that are downloaded to your computer. Cookies cannot damage your computer. Cookies, by themselves, cannot be used to identify you. Unless you've chosen to submit personal information to Tix though registration or the purchase of products and/or services, Tix cannot identify you. Cookies are used by Tix to allow the smooth operation of the Site and to track your activity so that we may tailor the content of the Site to match your interests.

**Changes** Tix may change this policy from time to time. Any changes will be posted on this Site.

**Terms of Use** Click here for our Terms of Use.
